<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ARIFOLIO</title>
    <link>https://amazonessari.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ARIFOLIO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 17:49:12 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://amazonessari.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Primal Bodycare</title>
      <link>https://amazonessari.github.io/primal-bodycare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 17:49:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amazonessari.github.io/primal-bodycare/</guid>
      <description>Overview My role Research Researched about the company and other LP by competitors
Wireframe Placed provided contents without color or assets in Figma
Design Designed statically including all assets in Figma
Code HTML, SCSS and JavaScript with Parcel
Launch Deployed the repository built by Parcel on server
  Members Takuya Shiomi - Director Prepared contents
Background</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PROGRIT</title>
      <link>https://amazonessari.github.io/progrit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 11:45:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amazonessari.github.io/progrit/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is a landing page for the internship recruitment of our external client.
My role Research Researched on the company
Wireframe Made the contents in Figma
Design Designed the static page in Figma
Code Coded in HTML, SCSS with the web application bundler Parcel
Launch Deployed the repository on the server of our client   Team Fumiya Sorimachi - Mentor Designer Gave me a feedback
Process &amp;mdash; Preparing &amp;mdash;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio Site</title>
      <link>https://amazonessari.github.io/portfolio-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 22:59:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amazonessari.github.io/portfolio-site/</guid>
      <description>Overview It is my first portfolio website that I designed and coded entirely to show my work. Built by open-source static site generators HUGO.
My role Research Researched on award winners websites, HUGO, and JavaScript
Wireframe Made all the contents in Figma
Design Designed the static page in Figma
Code Coded in HTML, SCSS, and pure JavaScript with HUGO
Process I made this portfolio website to expand job opportunities with attaching to my resume.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EoD</title>
      <link>https://amazonessari.github.io/eod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 22:58:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amazonessari.github.io/eod/</guid>
      <description>Overview EoD is a coaching firm specialized in leadership development. I designed the first official website for them with the design tool Studio.
My role Research About EoD and Studio
Design Static design in the tool Studio
  Team Fumiya Sorimachi - Mentor Designer Gave me a feedback
Takuya Shiomi - Director Prepared contents
Process Because EoD is our sister company, the client was committed as a director. We used the web design tool Studio for them to feel free to edit content after delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GeekSalon</title>
      <link>https://amazonessari.github.io/geeksalon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 22:58:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amazonessari.github.io/geeksalon/</guid>
      <description>Overview GeekSalon is a programming school for university students by our company. I designed a landing page for the trial event limited to female students.
My role Research Researched about GeekSalon, HTML, CSS, JavaScript
Wireframe Made all the contents in Figma
Design Designed the static page in Figma
Code Coded in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
Team Gordon Miyamoto - Senior Designer Gave me a feedback
Fumiya Sorimachi - Mentor Designer Gave me a feedback</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MANOMA</title>
      <link>https://amazonessari.github.io/manoma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 22:57:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amazonessari.github.io/manoma/</guid>
      <description>Overview MANOMA is a new smart home service provided by SONY. It equips with Amazon Alexa to enable voice control, and by inserting LTE SIM, you can easily have a wireless Internet environment without any settings. Our company sells it targeting 20’s. I designed a flyer as product descriptions used in face-to-face sales.
My role Research Researched on MANOMA, fundamentals of design, Photoshop, and Illustrator
Making a survey form Made a customer survey form on Google Spreadsheet that is comprehensive in many kinds of designs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Learned</title>
      <link>https://amazonessari.github.io/how-i-learned/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 12:23:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amazonessari.github.io/how-i-learned/</guid>
      <description>Before internship I have been into creativity in my entire life. When I was a little kid I used try to make anything from trash such as UFO catcher, a scale model and furniture.
It comes to aesthetics when to create anything. Beautiful stuffs attract me a lot, but I thought it is a natural born talent and there is nothing I can do. However I had a chance to learn design as an intern through my friend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>